kanarygifts.com 2015-10-23

# Privacy Policy - The Most Trusted Online Luxury Store in Middle East

The information we obtain through our website enables us to provide you with all the particulars specific to your interests and needs. Please continue reading to understand the type of information we collect through our website. Any references made to 'we', 'our' and 'us' indicate kanarygifts.com; the references such as 'you' and 'your' indicate the users and visitors of the website.

This privacy policy takes you through how we obtain, use and in some cases, disclose your information. It also deals with the measures we have taken to treat your information with safety. Lastly, this policy clarifies your choices with reference to collecting, using and disclosing your personal information. By visiting the website either directly or via another website, you agree to the practices mentioned in this policy.

Protecting user information is entirely the basis of trust, so your privacy is extremely valuable to us. We shall hence only use your personal information as explained in the privacy policy. We do not use your information unless it is necessary, so you can count on us to collect your information only if it is applicable to our deal with you.

We may collect various pieces of information if you seek to place an order for a product with us on the site. You are free to visit the website and browse without giving your details. During your visit to the website, you may stay unidentified and we can't recognize you anytime unless you register on the site or already logged in.

We do collect, assimilate and deal with your information to process your shopping on the website, any likely claims and to offer services, which you requested. You may have to dispense some information including but not limited to title, name, gender, email address, delivery address, contact numbers - both landline and mobile and payment details.

The information that you provide is also useful to :

  * Administer your account
  * Validate and complete transactions corresponding to payments that are done online
  * Review the downloading of data
  * Enhance the scheme and/or layout or content of different pages of our website and tailor them for better usability
  * Conduct research on demographics of our users
  * Observe the visitors on our website
  * Send all the information we believe you may find helpful or which you wanted from us

Depending on your consent to obtain information, we may contact you through email or phone with all the details and you always have the right to opt out any time of your selection.

#### **Third Parties**

We may also pass your name, phone and address to a third party to deliver the product to you (for instance to the courier company). Apart from this as mentioned in this Privacy Policy, we shall not reveal or sell your personal information to any third parties without your consent unless and until this is required for the purposes stated in this. Please understand that we are not accountable for the content or practices of those third parties, nor for any third party to whom we pass your information in their alignment with our Privacy Policy.

Payments that you make through the site will process by our International Network Agent. You must only submit to us or to our Agent, the Site information, which is accurate and clear. You must keep it up to date and inform us of any changes.

Your actual order details may be stored with us but for security reasons can be retrieved directly by us. However, you may access this information by logging into your account on the site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, personal information and newsletters to which you may have been subscribed to.

You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

#### **Cookies**

We use cookies for your convenience. Cookies are small text files with which our server identifies your computer as a user when you browse through certain pages on the website.

Your internet browser stores these files on your hard drive, and we recognize these files to recognize your IP address, thus saving your enough time, while you want to enter the website. You can always modify browser settings so as not to accept cookies, but this would certainly restrict your convenience of using the website. The cookies do not contain any confidential or personal information, and are even free from malicious viruses.

The preferred currency and website language are some of the details that our cookies track. We also store cookies with the purpose of mapping your interests with your geographical location, hence to be able to present a wide array of relevant options, which will make your shopping experience memorable. Acceptance of cookies is not a requirement to visit the website. However making an order is possible without the activation of cookies.

#### **Payment Security**

When our clients are interested to buy and register in our website, we collect their name, address, and phone information for shipping purpose only. We save their email address information to send the periodical newsletter if the customer is interested. We never save or have access to their payment information as they process through highly protected SSL gateways. We never share our client's information with any other third party organization.

We guarantee that our customers enjoy 100% secure transaction while they make an order from our website. Regardless of the payment method chosen, PayPal, Visa or Master Card, the information provided by you are made confidential and encrypted automatically while in transit from your computer to the SSL layer with a key length of 128-bits, which is the maximum level of encoding protection available commercially. Before you even sign up or log in to make payment, the server validates whether you’re browsing via an approved browser- the one which uses SSL 3.0 or higher.

Usually, once you finish filling up necessary details in the available fields, you will redirect to the payment site, where your information resides on a secure server that is not just physically very secure but electronically as well.

The payment servers which employed by these payment processing websites are guarded by a robust electronic firewall and remain secluded from the public computers on the internet, so you can make sure that your information is available only to the right payment gateway.

For e.g. once you confirm an order to be made via PayPal, you will navigate through PayPal for completing the payment and once you finish providing the information as required by PayPal, your transaction will be complete, following which you will be directed back to our website.

Note that at no point any information you entered into PayPal is stored on our servers. Hence, you can check out the security policy of PayPal to get more information on how it processes there.

Similarly, your credit card details are very safe and secure with us. Nobody can even try intercepting or reading your personal information because these are directly stored in a log on the secure server of the payment gateway and not our server.

While we are not able to pledge 100% security, this level of security makes it hard for even an expert hacker to decrypt your information. However, we suggest that you must not send us the information of your credit or debit card via unencrypted electronic channels with us such as emails and you are completely responsible for protecting yourself against unauthorized access to your computer and passwords.
